{
  "easy": [
    {
      "number": 1,
      "question": "What year did United win the Treble?",
      "option_a": "1968",
      "option_b": "1992",
      "option_c": "2008",
      "option_d": "1999",
      "correct": "1999"
    },
    {
      "number": 2,
      "question": "Which of these players has not worn the No. 7 shirt for United?",
      "option_a": "Wayne Rooney",
      "option_b": "Eric Cantona",
      "option_c": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "option_d": "David Beckham",
      "correct": "Wayne Rooney"
    },
    {
      "number": 3,
      "question": "Who is the most successful manager in United history?",
      "option_a": "Matt Busby",
      "option_b": "Jos√© Mourinho",
      "option_c": "Sir Alex Ferguson",
      "option_d": "Ron Atkinson",
      "correct": "Sir Alex Ferguson"
    },
    {
      "number": 4,
      "question": "How many times have we won the First Division/Premier League?",
      "option_a": "15",
      "option_b": "23",
      "option_c": "20",
      "option_d": "11",
      "correct": "20"
    },
    {
      "number": 5,
      "question": "Who is our all-time record Goalscorer?",
      "option_a": "Ruud Van Nistelrooy",
      "option_b": "Ryan Giggs",
      "option_c": "Paul Scholes",
      "option_d": "Wayne Rooney",
      "correct": "Wayne Rooney"
    },
    {
      "number": 6,
      "question": "How many times have we won the European Cup/Champions League?",
      "option_a": "7",
      "option_b": "3",
      "option_c": "1",
      "option_d": "8",
      "correct": "3"
    },
    {
      "number": 7,
      "question": "Manchester United was originally formed as ______________?",
      "option_a": "Newton Heath LYR",
      "option_b": "Dial Square",
      "option_c": "Hotspur Football Club",
      "option_d": "Sport-Club Juventus",
      "correct": "Newton Heath LYR"
    },
    {
      "number": 8,
      "question": "Manchester United beat ________ in the 1999 Champions League Final?",
      "option_a": "Real Madrid",
      "option_b": "Barcelona",
      "option_c": "Juventus",
      "option_d": "Bayern Munich",
      "correct": "Bayern Munich"
    },
    {
      "number": 9,
      "question": "Which player kung fu kicked a Crystal Palace fan in January 1995?",
      "option_a": "Mark Hughes",
      "option_b": "Paul Ince",
      "option_c": "Eric Cantona",
      "option_d": "Denis Irwin",
      "correct": "Eric Cantona"
    },
    {
      "number": 10,
      "question": "What was the final score in the 1999 Champtions League Final?",
      "option_a": "1-0",
      "option_b": "5-4",
      "option_c": "3-1",
      "option_d": "2-1",
      "correct": "2-1"
    },
    {
      "number": 11,
      "question": "What club was Eric Cantona signed from?",
      "option_a": "Leeds United",
      "option_b": "Portsmouth",
      "option_c": "Arsenal",
      "option_d": "West Ham",
      "correct": "Leeds United"
    },
    {
      "number": 12,
      "question": "Who is United's record Signing?",
      "option_a": "Carlos Tevez",
      "option_b": "Paul Pogba",
      "option_c": "David Beckham",
      "option_d": "Romelu Lukaku",
      "correct": "Paul Pogba"
    },
    {
      "number": 13,
      "question": "In what year was the Munich air crash?",
      "option_a": "1968",
      "option_b": "1958",
      "option_c": "1978",
      "option_d": "1948",
      "correct": "1958"
    },
    {
      "number": 14,
      "question": "How many times have United won the FA Cup?",
      "option_a": "3",
      "option_b": "6",
      "option_c": "12",
      "option_d": "9",
      "correct": "12"
    },
    {
      "number": 15,
      "question": "Who scored the winning goal in the 1999 Champions League Final?",
      "option_a": "Ryan Giggs",
      "option_b": "Jesper Blomqvist",
      "option_c": "Teddy Sheringham",
      "option_d": "Ole Gunnar Solskjaer",
      "correct": "Ole Gunnar Solskjaer"
    },
    {
      "number": 16,
      "question": "By what nickname were Manchester United known during the late 1950s?",
      "option_a": "The Flying Babes",
      "option_b": "The Wonder Babes",
      "option_c": "The Busby Babes",
      "option_d": "The Elder Babes",
      "correct": "The Busby Babes"
    },
    {
      "number": 17,
      "question": "By what score did Manchester United beat Ipswich Town in 1995?",
      "option_a": "3-1",
      "option_b": "5-1",
      "option_c": "9-0",
      "option_d": "3-2",
      "correct": "9-0"
    },
    {
      "number": 18,
      "question": "What is the name of Manchester United's home ground?",
      "option_a": "Maine Road",
      "option_b": "Old Trafford",
      "option_c": "City of Manchester Stadium",
      "option_d": "Anfield",
      "correct": "Old Trafford"
    },
    {
      "number": 19,
      "question": "Which of these numbers did David Beckham NOT wear at United?",
      "option_a": "24",
      "option_b": "13",
      "option_c": "7",
      "option_d": "10",
      "correct": "13"
    },
    {
      "number": 20,
      "question": "Which team did Anthony Martial score his debut United goal?",
      "option_a": "Manchester City",
      "option_b": "Tottenham Hotspur",
      "option_c": "Cardiff City",
      "option_d": "Liverpool",
      "correct": "Liverpool"
    },
    {
      "number": 21,
      "question": "How many goals did Wayne Rooney score on his United debut?",
      "option_a": "0",
      "option_b": "3",
      "option_c": "2",
      "option_d": "4",
      "correct": "3"
    },
    {
      "number": 22,
      "question": "Against which team did David Beckham score from the halfway line?",
      "option_a": "Tottenham Hotspur",
      "option_b": "Newcastle United",
      "option_c": "Wimbledon",
      "option_d": "Aston Villa",
      "correct": "Wimbledon"
    },
    {
      "number": 23,
      "question": "What year did Alex Ferguson take over as Manager?",
      "option_a": "1992",
      "option_b": "1980",
      "option_c": "1991",
      "option_d": "1986",
      "correct": "1986"
    },
    {
      "number": 24,
      "question": "In what year were the club now known as Manchester United formed?",
      "option_a": "1878",
      "option_b": "1890",
      "option_c": "1875",
      "option_d": "1885",
      "correct": "1878"
    },
    {
      "number": 25,
      "question": "What was the final score of the European cup Final in 1968?",
      "option_a": "3-1",
      "option_b": "2-1",
      "option_c": "4-1",
      "option_d": "4-2",
      "correct": "4-1"
    },
    {
      "number": 26,
      "question": "Who did Manchester United beat in the 2008 Champions League Final?",
      "option_a": "Liverpool",
      "option_b": "AC Milan",
      "option_c": "Chelsea",
      "option_d": "Barcelona",
      "correct": "Chelsea"
    },
    {
      "number": 27,
      "question": "Who scored the winning goal in the 1999 FA Cup Semi-Final against Arsenal?",
      "option_a": "David Beckham",
      "option_b": "Phil Neville",
      "option_c": "Roy Keane",
      "option_d": "Ryan Giggs",
      "correct": "Ryan Giggs"
    },
    {
      "number": 28,
      "question": "Which of these teams was not in our Champions League group in 1999?",
      "option_a": "Barcelona",
      "option_b": "AC Milan",
      "option_c": "Brondby",
      "option_d": "Bayern Munich",
      "correct": "AC Milan"
    },
    {
      "number": 29,
      "question": "Which of these players has not been a captain at Manchester United?",
      "option_a": "Roy Keane",
      "option_b": "Jesper Blomqvist",
      "option_c": "Peter Schmeichel",
      "option_d": "Ashley Young",
      "correct": "Jesper Blomqvist"
    },
    {
      "number": 30,
      "question": "Which player did not wear the number 20 shirt at United?",
      "option_a": "Louis Saha",
      "option_b": "Ole Gunnar Solskjaer",
      "option_c": "Rafael Da Silva",
      "option_d": "Robin Van Persie",
      "correct": "Louis Saha"
    },
    {
      "number": 31,
      "question": "How many goals did Eric Cantona score on his return to the United side against Liverpool after an 8 month ban?",
      "option_a": "2",
      "option_b": "1",
      "option_c": "3",
      "option_d": "5",
      "correct": "1"
    },
    {
      "number": 32,
      "question": "Marcus Rashord scored his first United penalty against which European club to complete a stunning comeback in the Champions League?",
      "option_a": "AC Milan",
      "option_b": "Real Madrid",
      "option_c": "Paris Saint Germain",
      "option_d": "Liverpool",
      "correct": "Paris Saint Germain"
    },
    {
      "number": 33,
      "question": "Marcus Rashford scored two goals on his Premiership debut against which club?",
      "option_a": "Tottenham Hotspur",
      "option_b": "Manchester City",
      "option_c": "Leicester City",
      "option_d": "Arsenal",
      "correct": "Arsenal"
    },
    {
      "number": 34,
      "question": "Which team did Manchester United beat in the 2017 Europa League Final?",
      "option_a": "Lyon",
      "option_b": "Celta Vigo",
      "option_c": "Anderlecht",
      "option_d": "Ajax",
      "correct": "Ajax"
    },
    {
      "number": 35,
      "question": "Which player scored the final penalty in the 2008 Champions League Final?",
      "option_a": "Anderson",
      "option_b": "Owen Hargreaves",
      "option_c": "Ryan Giggs",
      "option_d": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "correct": "Ryan Giggs"
    },
    {
      "number": 36,
      "question": "Which team did United pip to the 1998-99 Premier League title?",
      "option_a": "Liverpool",
      "option_b": "Arsenal",
      "option_c": "Chelsea",
      "option_d": "Aston Villa",
      "correct": "Arsenal"
    },
    {
      "number": 37,
      "question": "Which player did NOT score on their United debut?",
      "option_a": "Ruud Van Nistelrooy",
      "option_b": "Louis Saha",
      "option_c": "Ole Gunnar Solskjaer",
      "option_d": "Dwight Yorke",
      "correct": "Dwight Yorke"
    },
    {
      "number": 38,
      "question": "Which of these numbers has Marcus Rashford NOT worn since joining the first team?",
      "option_a": "7",
      "option_b": "10",
      "option_c": "19",
      "option_d": "39",
      "correct": "7"
    },
    {
      "number": 39,
      "question": "Manchester United's mascot is known as _____ The Red?",
      "option_a": "Fred",
      "option_b": "Alex",
      "option_c": "Paul",
      "option_d": "Norman",
      "correct": "Fred"
    },
    {
      "number": 40,
      "question": "What was the shirt most often worn by George Best during his career at Manchester United?",
      "option_a": "8",
      "option_b": "10",
      "option_c": "7",
      "option_d": "11",
      "correct": "7"
    },
    {
      "number": 41,
      "question": "Who was manager of Manchester United between from 1946 to 1969?",
      "option_a": "Sir Matt Busby",
      "option_b": "Sir Alex Ferguson",
      "option_c": "Jose Mourinho",
      "option_d": "Ron Atkinson",
      "correct": "Sir Matt Busby"
    },
    {
      "number": 42,
      "question": "Who scored United's goal in the Champions League Final in 2008?",
      "option_a": "Wayne Rooney",
      "option_b": "Carlos Tevez",
      "option_c": "Michael Carrick",
      "option_d": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "correct": "Cristiano Ronaldo"
    },
    {
      "number": 43,
      "question": "The date was 28th August 2011 and the final result was 8-2. Wayne Rooney scored his 6th hat-trick for club. Which team was Manchester United playing against?",
      "option_a": "Liverpool",
      "option_b": "Arsenal",
      "option_c": "Tottenham Hotspur",
      "option_d": "West Ham United",
      "correct": "Arsenal"
    },
    {
      "number": 44,
      "question": "Alex Ferguson is known for his bad temper. In 2003 he kicked a boot, which hit a player and cut him above his eye. The cut required stitches. Who was the player?",
      "option_a": "David Beckham",
      "option_b": "Diego Forlan",
      "option_c": "Wayne Rooney",
      "option_d": "Ruud Van Nistelrooy",
      "correct": "David Beckham"
    },
    {
      "number": 45,
      "question": "Which of these players did not play for the 1992 FA Cup Youth team?",
      "option_a": "David Beckham",
      "option_b": "Gary Neville",
      "option_c": "Nicky Butt",
      "option_d": "Roy Keane",
      "correct": "Roy Keane"
    },
    {
      "number": 46,
      "question": "A statue called 'The United Trinity' stands outside Old Trafford, featuring, Denis Law, George best and which other player?",
      "option_a": "Sir Bobby Charlton",
      "option_b": "Brian Kidd",
      "option_c": "Nobby Stiles",
      "option_d": "Bill Foulkes",
      "correct": "Sir Bobby Charlton"
    },
    {
      "number": 47,
      "question": "Manchester United's record Champions League win came in 2007 against Roma. What was the score?",
      "option_a": "8-2",
      "option_b": "9-0",
      "option_c": "6-3",
      "option_d": "7-1",
      "correct": "7-1"
    },
    {
      "number": 48,
      "question": "As of December 2022, who is the current Manchester United Manager?",
      "option_a": "Jose Mourinho",
      "option_b": "Pep Guardiola",
      "option_c": "Jurgen Klopp",
      "option_d": "Erik Ten Hag",
      "correct": "Erik Ten Hag"
    },
    {
      "number": 49,
      "question": "Which of these has not been a shirt sponsor?",
      "option_a": "Sharp Electronics",
      "option_b": "Etihad",
      "option_c": "Vodafone",
      "option_d": "AIG",
      "correct": "Etihad"
    },
    {
      "number": 50,
      "question": "The club's current Womens football team was founded in which year?",
      "option_a": "2018",
      "option_b": "2019",
      "option_c": "2020",
      "option_d": "2021",
      "correct": "2018"
    },
    {
      "number": 51,
      "question": "Following a 3-1 defeat in the opening game of the 1995-96 league season, which TV football pundit famously said of Manchester United, and Sir Alex Ferguson, that 'You win nothing with kids'?",
      "option_a": "Gary Lineker",
      "option_b": "Alan Hansen",
      "option_c": "Andy Gray",
      "option_d": "Jimmy Hill",
      "correct": "Alan Hansen"
    },
    {
      "number": 52,
      "question": "Sir Alex Ferguson retired from management at the end of the 2012-13 season, after 27 years in charge of Manchester United. Which team did Manchester United face in his last game in charge?",
      "option_a": "Wigan Athletic",
      "option_b": "Stoke City",
      "option_c": "Swansea City",
      "option_d": "West Bromwich Albion",
      "correct": "West Bromwich Albion"
    },
    {
      "number": 53,
      "question": "Sir Alex Ferguson led Manchester United to two UEFA Champions League finals in 2009 and 2011. Who did they lose to in both finals?",
      "option_a": "AC Milan",
      "option_b": "Real Madrid",
      "option_c": "Juventus",
      "option_d": "Barcelona",
      "correct": "Barcelona"
    },
    {
      "number": 54,
      "question": "What was the final score in Sir Alex Ferguson's last Manchester United game in charge?",
      "option_a": "3-1",
      "option_b": "5-1",
      "option_c": "5-5",
      "option_d": "2-1",
      "correct": "5-5"
    },
    {
      "number": 55,
      "question": "What was Bryan Robson's nickname?",
      "option_a": "Captain Marvel",
      "option_b": "Choccy",
      "option_c": "Butch",
      "option_d": "El Beatle",
      "correct": "Captain Marvel"
    },
    {
      "number": 56,
      "question": "Who's nickname was 'El Beatle'?",
      "option_a": "Sir Bobby Charlton",
      "option_b": "Denis Law",
      "option_c": "George Best",
      "option_d": "Nobby Stiles",
      "correct": "George Best"
    },
    {
      "number": 57,
      "question": "I was known as 'The Great Dane'. Who am I?",
      "option_a": "Peter Schmeichel",
      "option_b": "Ronny Johnsen",
      "option_c": "Nikki Jovanovic",
      "option_d": "John Sivebaek",
      "correct": "Peter Schmeichel"
    },
    {
      "number": 58,
      "question": "Which player admitted in his autobiography that he intended to hurt Alf-Inge Haland in a knee-high foul, which saw him sent off during a match against Manchester City in 2001?",
      "option_a": "Eric Cantona",
      "option_b": "Steve Bruce",
      "option_c": "Ryan Giggs",
      "option_d": "Roy Keane",
      "correct": "Roy Keane"
    },
    {
      "number": 59,
      "question": "Which player failed to attend a drug test in 2003, receiving a large fine and an 8 month ban?",
      "option_a": "Wayne Rooney",
      "option_b": "Gary Neville",
      "option_c": "Rio Ferdinand",
      "option_d": "Paul Scholes",
      "correct": "Rio Ferdinand"
    },
    {
      "number": 60,
      "question": "Which one of these describes the Manchester United badge?",
      "option_a": "Blue and white with a yellow lion",
      "option_b": "Red and white with a phoenix",
      "option_c": "A castle turret with 2 wreaths",
      "option_d": "Red and yellow. A devil holding a fork with a ship",
      "correct": "Red and yellow. A devil holding a fork with a ship"
    },
    {
      "number": 61,
      "question": "Which Manchester United player became the first ever player to be crowned PFA young young player of the year in 1992?",
      "option_a": "David Beckham",
      "option_b": "Paul Scholes",
      "option_c": "Robbie Savage",
      "option_d": "Ryan Giggs",
      "correct": "Ryan Giggs"
    },
    {
      "number": 62,
      "question": "As of December 2022, which England Womens European Championship winner wears the number 7 for United Womens?",
      "option_a": "Alessia Russo",
      "option_b": "Leah Galton",
      "option_c": "Nikita Parris",
      "option_d": "Ella Toone",
      "correct": "Ella Toone"
    },
    {
      "number": 63,
      "question": "As of December 2022, who is the current captain of United's Womens team?",
      "option_a": "Alessia Russo",
      "option_b": "Maya Le Tissier",
      "option_c": "Katie Zelem",
      "option_d": "Ella Toone",
      "correct": "Katie Zelem"
    },
    {
      "number": 64,
      "question": "Who was the first player to win the Sir Matt Busby Player of the Year award in 3 consecutive years and the first Goalkeeper to win it?",
      "option_a": "David De Gea",
      "option_b": "Fabien Barthez",
      "option_c": "Edwin Van Der Sar",
      "option_d": "Peter Schmeichel",
      "correct": "David De Gea"
    },
    {
      "number": 65,
      "question": "Who was the leading scorer for United on their way to winning the 2008 UEFA Champions League?",
      "option_a": "Carlos Tevez",
      "option_b": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "option_c": "Wayne Rooney",
      "option_d": "Paul Scholes",
      "correct": "Cristiano Ronaldo"
    },
    {
      "number": 66,
      "question": "Who scored two goals, including the winner, as United won the EFL Cup by beating Southampton 3-2 in 2017?",
      "option_a": "Anthony Martial",
      "option_b": "Juan Mata",
      "option_c": "Jesse Lingard",
      "option_d": "Zlatan Ibrahimovic",
      "correct": "Zlatan Ibrahimovic"
    },
    {
      "number": 67,
      "question": "Bruno Fernandes was signed from which Portuguese Club?",
      "option_a": "Benfica",
      "option_b": "Boavista",
      "option_c": "Porto",
      "option_d": "Sporting Lisbon",
      "correct": "Sporting Lisbon"
    },
    {
      "number": 68,
      "question": "Against which team did Bruno Fernandes score his first Manchester United goal?",
      "option_a": "Arsenal",
      "option_b": "Chelsea",
      "option_c": "Watford",
      "option_d": "Tottenham Hotspur",
      "correct": "Watford"
    },
    {
      "number": 69,
      "question": "Against which club did Antony make his debut and score his first goal for Manchester United?",
      "option_a": "Chelsea",
      "option_b": "Arsenal",
      "option_c": "Liverpool",
      "option_d": "Manchester City",
      "correct": "Arsenal"
    },
    {
      "number": 70,
      "question": "Robin Van Persie scored his first Manchester United goal against which club?",
      "option_a": "Fulham",
      "option_b": "Arsenal",
      "option_c": "Everton",
      "option_d": "Liverpool",
      "correct": "Fulham"
    },
    {
      "number": 71,
      "question": "Which player got sent off in Sir Alex Ferguson's last UEFA Champions League game?",
      "option_a": "Rio Ferdinand",
      "option_b": "Michael Carrick",
      "option_c": "Nani",
      "option_d": "Wayne Rooney",
      "correct": "Nani"
    },
    {
      "number": 72,
      "question": "Which manager took over after Sir Alex Ferguson?",
      "option_a": "Jose Mourinho",
      "option_b": "Ole Gunnar Solskjaer",
      "option_c": "Erik Ten Hag",
      "option_d": "David Moyes",
      "correct": "David Moyes"
    },
    {
      "number": 73,
      "question": "Marcus Rashford made his debut for Manchester United in which year?",
      "option_a": "2014",
      "option_b": "2015",
      "option_c": "2016",
      "option_d": "2017",
      "correct": "2016"
    },
    {
      "number": 74,
      "question": "David De Gea made his Manchester United debut in which year?",
      "option_a": "2009",
      "option_b": "2010",
      "option_c": "2011",
      "option_d": "2012",
      "correct": "2011"
    },
    {
      "number": 75,
      "question": "Who missed the penalty which cost us the 2020/2021 UEFA Europa League trophy?",
      "option_a": "Bruno Fernandes",
      "option_b": "Marcus Rashford",
      "option_c": "Edison Cavani",
      "option_d": "David De Gea",
      "correct": "David De Gea"
    },
    {
      "number": 76,
      "question": "Robin Van Persie was signed from which fellow Premier League club?",
      "option_a": "Tottenham Hotspur",
      "option_b": "Newcastle United",
      "option_c": "Arsenal",
      "option_d": "Liverpool",
      "correct": "Arsenal"
    },
    {
      "number": 77,
      "question": "Juan Mata signed from which fellow Premier League club?",
      "option_a": "Manchester City",
      "option_b": "Chelsea",
      "option_c": "Liverpool",
      "option_d": "Tottenham Hotspur",
      "correct": "Chelsea"
    },
    {
      "number": 78,
      "question": "Which one of these players did not come through the Manchester United Academy?",
      "option_a": "Marcus Rashford",
      "option_b": "Scott McTominay",
      "option_c": "Danny Welbeck",
      "option_d": "Anthony Martial",
      "correct": "Anthony Martial"
    },
    {
      "number": 79,
      "question": "Who was United's top scorer in the 2021/2022 season?",
      "option_a": "Marcus Rashford",
      "option_b": "Bruno Fernandes",
      "option_c": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "option_d": "Jadon Sancho",
      "correct": "Cristiano Ronaldo"
    },
    {
      "number": 80,
      "question": "Who was our leading top scorer in the 1998/99 treble winning season?",
      "option_a": "Dwight Yorke",
      "option_b": "Ole Gunnar Solskjaer",
      "option_c": "Teddy Sheringham",
      "option_d": "Andy Cole",
      "correct": "Dwight Yorke"
    },
    {
      "number": 81,
      "question": "Who was the first Manager of the current Manchester United Womens team?",
      "option_a": "Mark Skinner",
      "option_b": "Phil Neville",
      "option_c": "Casey Stoney",
      "option_d": "Sarina Wiegman",
      "correct": "Casey Stoney"
    },
    {
      "number": 82,
      "question": "Which one of these players is not an Academy graduate from the United Womens Academy?",
      "option_a": "Katie Zelem",
      "option_b": "Ella Toone",
      "option_c": "Millie Turner",
      "option_d": "Adriana Leon",
      "correct": "Adriana Leon"
    },
    {
      "number": 83,
      "question": "Which of these Manchester United Womens players did NOT play for the English National team in their 2022 Womens European Championship win?",
      "option_a": "Katie Zelem",
      "option_b": "Ella Toone",
      "option_c": "Alessia Russo",
      "option_d": "Mary Earps",
      "correct": "Katie Zelem"
    },
    {
      "number": 84,
      "question": "Who was our captain from 1982-1994?",
      "option_a": "Steve Bruce",
      "option_b": "Eric Cantona",
      "option_c": "Bryan Robson",
      "option_d": "Eric Cantona",
      "correct": "Bryan Robson"
    },
    {
      "number": 85,
      "question": "United beat which team in the FA Cup Final 2-0 of the 1998/99 Treble winning season?",
      "option_a": "Middlesbrough",
      "option_b": "Newcastle United",
      "option_c": "Southampton",
      "option_d": "Wimbledon",
      "correct": "Newcastle United"
    },
    {
      "number": 86,
      "question": "Who was captain of the team against Bayern Munich in the 1999 UEFA Champions League Final?",
      "option_a": "Roy Keane",
      "option_b": "David Beckham",
      "option_c": "Denis Irwin",
      "option_d": "Peter Schmeichel",
      "correct": "Peter Schmeichel"
    },
    {
      "number": 87,
      "question": "Who scored the final goal at Old Trafford in Sir alex Ferguson's last game in charge there?",
      "option_a": "Rio Ferdinand",
      "option_b": "Javier Hernandez",
      "option_c": "Ryan Giggs",
      "option_d": "Robin Van Persie",
      "correct": "Rio Ferdinand"
    },
    {
      "number": 88,
      "question": "Jaap Stam was brought in from which Dutch side?",
      "option_a": "Ajax",
      "option_b": "SBV Vitesse Arnhem",
      "option_c": "PSV Eindhoven",
      "option_d": "Feyenoord",
      "correct": "PSV Eindhoven"
    },
    {
      "number": 89,
      "question": "Who scored the winning goal against Tottenham Hotspory to crown United Champions in the 1998/99 season?",
      "option_a": "David Beckham",
      "option_b": "Paul Scholes",
      "option_c": "Nicky Butt",
      "option_d": "Andy Cole",
      "correct": "Andy Cole"
    },
    {
      "number": 90,
      "question": "Which player did Wayne Rooney surpass to become United's all-time leading scorer?",
      "option_a": "Jack Rowley",
      "option_b": "Sir Bobby Charlton",
      "option_c": "Denis Law",
      "option_d": "George Best",
      "correct": "Sir Bobby Charlton"
    },
    {
      "number": 91,
      "question": "Which Brazilian twin brothers played for Manchester United?",
      "option_a": "Fred & Antony",
      "option_b": "Rafael & Fabio",
      "option_c": "Casemiro & Telles",
      "option_d": "Anderson & Possebon",
      "correct": "Rafael & Fabio"
    },
    {
      "number": 92,
      "question": "In what year was Old Trafford built?",
      "option_a": "1910",
      "option_b": "1915",
      "option_c": "1920",
      "option_d": "1925",
      "correct": "1910"
    },
    {
      "number": 93,
      "question": "The West Stand of Old Trafford is more famously known as what?",
      "option_a": "Sir Bobby Charlton Stand",
      "option_b": "Sir Alex Ferguson Stand",
      "option_c": "Stretford End",
      "option_d": "George Best Stand",
      "correct": "Stretford End"
    },
    {
      "number": 94,
      "question": "Old Trafford is situated on what road?",
      "option_a": "Sir Bobby Charlton Way",
      "option_b": "Sir Matt Busby Way",
      "option_c": "Sir Alex Ferguson Way",
      "option_d": "Denis Law Way",
      "correct": "Sir Matt Busby Way"
    },
    {
      "number": 95,
      "question": "In Manchester United's 2008 Champions League final victory over Chelsea on penalties, who was the only Red Devils player to miss a spot-kick?",
      "option_a": "Owen Hargreavwes",
      "option_b": "Anderson",
      "option_c": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "option_d": "Carlos Tevez",
      "correct": "Cristiano Ronaldo"
    },
    {
      "number": 96,
      "question": "Which Manchester United manager was said by fans to be 'at the wheel'?",
      "option_a": "Erik Ten Hag",
      "option_b": "Michael Carrick",
      "option_c": "David Moyes",
      "option_d": "Ole Gunnar Solskjaer",
      "correct": "Ole Gunnar Solskjaer"
    },
    {
      "number": 97,
      "question": "Who said: 'When the seagulls follow the trawler, it's because they think sardines will be thrown into the sea'?",
      "option_a": "Peter Schmeichel",
      "option_b": "Paul Ince",
      "option_c": "Eric Cantona",
      "option_d": "Gary Neville",
      "correct": "Eric Cantona"
    },
    {
      "number": 98,
      "question": "What is the nickname of Old Trafford?",
      "option_a": "The Theatre of Dreams",
      "option_b": "The Wonderland of Dreams",
      "option_c": "The Palace of Dreams",
      "option_d": "The Home of Dreams",
      "correct": "The Theatre of Dreams"
    },
    {
      "number": 99,
      "question": "Which player took the No. 7 jersey after Cristiano Ronaldo left?",
      "option_a": "Antonio Valencia",
      "option_b": "Michael Owen",
      "option_c": "Angel Di Maria",
      "option_d": "Jadon Sancho",
      "correct": "Michael Owen"
    },
    {
      "number": 100,
      "question": "Which player holds the distinction of being Manchester United's longest-serving captain?",
      "option_a": "Eric Cantona",
      "option_b": "Wayne Rooney",
      "option_c": "Bryan Robson",
      "option_d": "Steve Bruce",
      "correct": "Bryan Robson"
    }
  ]
}
